<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Laquysoft</title>
    <link>http://laquysoft.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Laquysoft</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Untitled</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2014 21:47:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://laquysoft.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Dart Book Review</title>
      <link>http://laquysoft.com/2014/12/17/mastering-dart-book-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2014 21:47:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://laquysoft.com/2014/12/17/mastering-dart-book-review/</guid>
      <description>Dart community is growing so much and many books about this wonderful web oriented language are borning.
I read quite all of them and they all covered the basic of the language and the development platform. To go in depth to the full power of Dart we need to join the discussions all over the web ( G+ Dartisans Community, StackOverflow, Google Groups etc. ).
&amp;ldquo;Mastering Dart&amp;rdquo; will help you to go beyond the &amp;ldquo;Hello world&amp;rdquo; code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows Phone Laquysoft App</title>
      <link>http://laquysoft.com/2013/12/16/windows-phone-laquysoft-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://laquysoft.com/2013/12/16/windows-phone-laquysoft-app/</guid>
      <description>**And Now **&amp;#8230;Laquysoft App for Windows Phone is out!
Now you can follow our blog from your Windows Phone stay tuned for more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows 8 Laquysoft App</title>
      <link>http://laquysoft.com/2013/12/14/windows-8-laquysoft-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://laquysoft.com/2013/12/14/windows-8-laquysoft-app/</guid>
      <description>Laquysoft App for Windows 8 is out!
Now you can follow our blog in a new richer experience, more will follow, stay tuned!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Connectivity: Quick-Union</title>
      <link>http://laquysoft.com/2013/09/30/dynamic-connectivity-quick-union/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://laquysoft.com/2013/09/30/dynamic-connectivity-quick-union/</guid>
      <description>Understood Quick-Find algorithm is too slow if we have many union operations. We have to design a new algorithm to do better, let&amp;#8217;s use a lazy approach where we try to avoid doing work until we have to:
we could think the array as a set of trees where each entry contains a reference to its parent in the tree. Each element of the array has associated with it a root and we can say that two elements are connected if they have the same root.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Connectivity: Quick-Find</title>
      <link>http://laquysoft.com/2013/09/21/dynamic-connectivity-quick-find/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://laquysoft.com/2013/09/21/dynamic-connectivity-quick-find/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;#8217;s assume our object can be identified by an integer number, we can use an integer Array as data structure for our solution (id[]) . In Quick-Find we consider two sites p and q are in the same component if id[p] is equal do id[q].
The initQuickFindUF function allocates the zeroed array and assign the slice that refers to that array to Elements; then go through it and set the value corresponding to each index ( *Elements[i] = i *).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Start</title>
      <link>http://laquysoft.com/2013/09/21/lets-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://laquysoft.com/2013/09/21/lets-start/</guid>
      <description>Let’s start this new adventure in blogger-land with a series of post about Algorithms and Go. I choose this two characters because of two targets, to learn a new language ( Go ) and renew my neurons about the classic algorithms studied in the past; I want to mix an old ingredient with a new one. I’m sure this road could take me to perceive new approaches to common problems, and i’m sure this trip is going to be funny.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>